PRIVACY POLICY

We attach great importance to the protection of your personal data and privacy rights on the Internet.

Please read our privacy policy. We aim to clarify how we handle your personal data, what information

we store and how we use it.

1\. INFORMATION ON PROCESSING AND PROTECTION OF PERSONAL DATA

1.1 Protecting your personal data is very important to us, so we always proceed in compliance

with applicable laws and international standards.

1.2 In connection with the adoption of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and

of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing

of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC

(GDPR), which, with effect as of 25 May 2018, applies to the processing of your personal data by

our company, TISCALI MEDIA, a.s., Company ID No.: 28516117, with its registered office at

Vá clavské ná m. 813/57, Prague 1 110 00 (hereinafter “TISCALI MEDIA” or “we”, “us”), the

operator of the Uschovna.cz service, we provide below a summary of basic information about the

processing and protection of your personal data by Uschovna.cz.

2\. WHAT PERSONAL DATA WE PROCESS AND HOW WE OBTAIN THEM

2.1 The personal data we process about you and their scope differ, in particular, according to the

purpose and the services provided:

2.1.1 For the purpose of performing data sending and collection services

(a) Contact details (e-mail address)

(b) IP address

(c) Recipients’ e-mail addresses

(d) Files sent

(e) Number of downloads of individual files including the IP addresses from where they

were downloaded

2.1.2 For the purpose of performing the data sending and collection service of Uschovna Plus

(a) Identification data (first name, surname, address)

(b) Contact details (e-mail address, phone number)

(c) Company name, Company ID No., Tax ID No., registered office

2.1.3 For the purpose of web server security

(a) Information about visiting our website (IP address)

2.1.4 Inordertoimproveourservicesandoffer

(b) Information about visiting our website (cookies, IP address)

2.1.5 Formarketingpurposesincludingsendingbusinessmessagesandpersonalisingads 1

(a) Information about visiting our website (cookies, IP address)

(b) Contact details (e-mail address)

2.2 We collect personal data directly from senders (when using the service), from registered users

upon registration, and based on your visits to our website (see the cookies section below).

3\. HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

3.1 We use your personal data, in particular, for the following purposes:

(a) Performing the selected service;

(b) Communicating with you and managing our contractual relationship;

(c) Addressing your complaints;

(d) Compliance with our statutory obligations; and

(e) Keeping you informed about changes and news in the products and services provided

and our personalised offers.

3.2 If it is necessary for the conclusion and performance of the contract or for the protection of our

legitimate interests related to the conclusion or performance of the contract, we use technology

mainly to create your customer profiles for the above purposes based on your consent or if

permitted by the law that also protects your rights.

3.3 We only retain your personal data for as long as any of the aforementioned purposes of

processing last(s) and, after that, only for the period and under the terms in compliance with

applicable laws and regulations.

3.4 In case you grant consent for marketing purposes (including possible profiling for the purpose

of offering suitable goods and services and processing of cookies), we retain your personal data

for 1 year after the consent was granted or from the last use of our services. In all other cases, the

processing period follows from the purpose of processing or is laid down by law.

4\. LEGAL BASIS FOR PERSONAL DATA PROCESSING

4.1 The legal basis that allows us to process your personal data depends on the purpose for

which we process the personal data. Therefore, we may process your personal data without your

consent in a specific case because:

(a) It is necessary for the purpose of concluding or performing the contract with you;

(b) It is necessary to fulfil our statutory obligations (e.g. in the area of accounting and

taxation);

(c) It is necessary to protect our legitimate interests (e.g. in connection with the exercise

of claims under concluded contracts or in connection with the analysis and improvement

of our services);

4.2 We may process your personal data for direct marketing purposes, i.e. offering our products,

reporting on news or other relevant business communications by sending them to your e-mail

address. You may revoke your consent to such use of your personal data at any time by sending a

notice of revocation to our e-mail address or clicking the link in the footer of any e-mail sent by us.

5\. TO WHOM WE PROVIDE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

5.1 We may provide your personal data to:

(a) Service providers who provide us with services related to our activities, especially

payment intermediaries, hosting companies and companies administering technology and

providing technical support;

(b) Other persons in accordance with applicable law (e.g. notifications to tax authorities in

cases specified by law, the police in criminal investigation etc.).

5.2 Your personal data may be transferred and stored within the countries of the European

Economic Area (the “EEA”), which are considered as having a comparable level of personal data

protection to that of the Czech Republic.

6\. WHAT ARE COOKIES AND HOW WE USE THEM

6.1 Cookies are small data files that are necessary for the website to function properly, which we

thus place in your computer, just like most websites. They are text files that websites store in your

computer or mobile device when you start using the website.

6.2 The website will thus remember, for some time, the actions and settings you made on the

website - for example, login information. Therefore, you do not need to re-enter this information

when you re-visit the website or switch between website sections.

6.3 We also use cookies to collect statistical data and personalise ads so that we can further

refine our website and improve the services we offer. Therefore, we share the information about

how you use our website with our advertising and analysis partners, namely Google and Tiscali

Media. You can find how Google handles cookies at

https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/cookies/.

6.4 In the case of your disagreement with the use of cookies and data obtained through our

website using cookies for the purposes stated above, you can:

(a) Block the use of cookies in the settings of your Internet browser or other computer program

(i.e. set your Internet browser or other computer program to block or disable cookies).

7\. YOUR RIGHTS

7.1 You have particularly the following rights in connection with the processing of your personal data:

(a) The right to clear, transparent and understandable information about how we use your

personal data and what your rights are;

(b) The right of access to personal data and other information related to their processing by the

Company;

(c) The right to rectify incorrect and incomplete personal data;

(d) The right to erase your personal data, especially if (i) they are no longer required for further

processing; (ii) you have withdrawn your consent to processing; (iii) you have legitimately objected

to their processing; (iv) the data have been processed unlawfully; or (v) the data must be erased

by law;

(e) The right to restrict the processing of your personal data if (i) you challenge the accuracy of

your personal data until we have verified their accuracy; (ii) processing is unlawful; (iii) we do not

need the data any longer but you need them for the purposes of exercising your legal

entitlements, or (iv) you object to their processing until we have verified that our legitimate reasons

outweigh your interests;

(f) The right to object to the processing of your personal data if we process them (i) for direct

marketing purposes, or (ii) for the purposes of our legitimate interests;

(g) The right to obtain your personal data and transfer them to another service provider;

(h) The right to file a complaint with the Office for Personal Data Protection, Pplk. Sochora 27,

170 00 Prague 7; www.uoou.cz

7.2 If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please contact us using the contact details given

below.

8\. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA

8.1 To ensure the security and confidentiality of your personal data, which is extremely important

to us, we use technical and organisational measures to protect against unauthorised access to

and misuse of data, to ensure the security of our IT systems and to recover data in the event of an

incident. We use encryption to protect your data where appropriate. All measures are regularly

reviewed and updated.

8.2 We process personal data manually as well as in electronic information systems that are

subject to physical, technical and procedural control. For data protection, we have a security

mechanism in place, including technical, organisational and personnel measures, and we require

the same level of protection from our processors.

9\. IN CASE YOU NEED FURTHER INFORMATION OR WANT TO EXERCISE YOUR RIGHTS

9.1 The full version of our Privacy Policy is available at www.uschovna.cz.

9.2 If you have any questions regarding the processing of your personal data, you need any other

related assistance, or you want to exercise your rights, please contact the responsible person in

the field of personal data protection electronically by e-mail info@uschovna.cz or in writing at the

above-mentioned address of the Company.
